https://mycollegeguide.org/privacypolicy

Select Degree Level
Associate'sBachelor'sMaster'sDoctorateCertificate / DiplomaPost GraduateHigh School and BelowNon Degree
2. Select a Category
Category
Art and DesignBusinessCommunicationsComputers and TechnologyCosmetologyCriminal Justice, Legal and SafetyCulinary ArtsEducation and TeachingEngineering and ArchitectureHealthcareHigh SchoolLiberal ArtsMath and SciencePsychology and CounselingTestingVocational and Trade
3. Select a Subject
Subject
Online Degree CategoriesBecome a Professional Photographer with Online Photography ClassesBest Online Associates Degree & ProgramsBest Online Bachelor’s Degrees & ProgramsBest Online Doctoral Programs & DegreesConsidering Getting an Online Exercise Science Degree?Earning an Online Computer Science DegreeGet your Medical Degree Through Online Medical SchoolGet Your Online Game Design DegreeGet Your PMP, Take Project Management Courses OnlineGuide to Online Law Degree & ProgramsIs Going Back to College Worth It?Online Architecture DegreesOnline Art and Design DegreesOnline Biology DegreesOnline Business DegreesOnline Communications DegreesOnline Counseling DegreesOnline Criminal Justice DegreesOnline Culinary Arts DegreesOnline Cyber Security Courses & DegreesOnline Economics DegreesOnline Education & Teaching DegreesOnline Engineering DegreesOnline English DegreesOnline Finance DegreesOnline General Studies DegreesOnline Graphic Design DegreesOnline Healthcare DegreesOnline History DegreesOnline Human Resources DegreesOnline Information Technology IT DegreeOnline IT DegreeOnline Journalism DegreesOnline Liberal Arts DegreesOnline Marketing DegreesOnline Master’s DegreeOnline Mathematics DegreesOnline Nursing DegreesOnline Nutrition DegreesOnline Political Science DegreesOnline Psychology DegreesOnline Science DegreesOnline Social Work DegreesOnline Theology DegreesOnline Vocational Training ProgramsOnline Web Design ProgramsTake Real Estate Classes Online to Get Your DegreeThe Complete Online Health Science Degree GuideTop 12 Online Healthcare DegreesWhat Can You Do With A Psychology Degree?What Can You Do With an Online Accounting Degree?What is Online Education?What to Know About Online Certificate Programs (Complete Guide)
Privacy Policy
by Michael Gluckstern
My College Guide Privacy Policy. We do not obtain any personal information about you unless you choose to share it.
What information do we collect?
We do not obtain any personal information about you unless you choose to share it. We collect information from you when you register on our site, fill out a form or request information from one of our colleges or companies.
When requesting information or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, date of birth and other personally identifiable information.. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
Like most websites, we use cookies to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website. Please refer to the ‘do we use cookies?’ section below for information about cookies and how we use them. When feasible, we do collect your IP address and the URLs that you come from or leave to.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
To furnish to colleges, companies and other advertisers from whom you have requested information as well as to our marketing partners. The colleges and companies and our marketing partners will then provide information to you directly. If you join our email list, we may share your information with any of our colleges, companies and marketing partners.
To provide products, programs and services you have requested.
To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
To send periodic emails. If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include college news, updates, related product or service information, etc, as well as information from our advertisers and marketing partners.
If you use our community section, any personally identifiable information you submit can be read, collected or used by other users of the forums. We are not responsible for any personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. See the “Terms of Use” section of our site.
Do we use cookies?
We also may allow third-party advertisers to track advertisements appearing on our site by using cookies to measure advertising effectiveness. (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.) We have no control over these third party cookies.
We may use cookies and to help us compile data and information about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. Cookies are not tied to personally identifiable information. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information except as described in this privacy statement. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. We also have the right to sell this information as part of a sale or all or substantially all of our assets.
Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
Age Issues
We do not knowingly accept or collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. If you are under 13 please do not use our site.
Terms and Conditions
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at https://mycollegeguide.org/termsofuse.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy contact us.
This policy was last modified on 2/24/2016.
Online Degree CategoriesBecome a Professional Photographer with Online Photography ClassesBest Online Associates Degree & ProgramsBest Online Bachelor’s Degrees & ProgramsBest Online Doctoral Programs & DegreesConsidering Getting an Online Exercise Science Degree?Earning an Online Computer Science DegreeGet your Medical Degree Through Online Medical SchoolGet Your Online Game Design DegreeGet Your PMP, Take Project Management Courses OnlineGuide to Online Law Degree & ProgramsIs Going Back to College Worth It?Online Architecture DegreesOnline Art and Design DegreesOnline Biology DegreesOnline Business DegreesOnline Communications DegreesOnline Counseling DegreesOnline Criminal Justice DegreesOnline Culinary Arts DegreesOnline Cyber Security Courses & DegreesOnline Economics DegreesOnline Education & Teaching DegreesOnline Engineering DegreesOnline English DegreesOnline Finance DegreesOnline General Studies DegreesOnline Graphic Design DegreesOnline Healthcare DegreesOnline History DegreesOnline Human Resources DegreesOnline Information Technology IT DegreeOnline IT DegreeOnline Journalism DegreesOnline Liberal Arts DegreesOnline Marketing DegreesOnline Master’s DegreeOnline Mathematics DegreesOnline Nursing DegreesOnline Nutrition DegreesOnline Political Science DegreesOnline Psychology DegreesOnline Science DegreesOnline Social Work DegreesOnline Theology DegreesOnline Vocational Training ProgramsOnline Web Design ProgramsTake Real Estate Classes Online to Get Your DegreeThe Complete Online Health Science Degree GuideTop 12 Online Healthcare DegreesWhat Can You Do With A Psychology Degree?What Can You Do With an Online Accounting Degree?What is Online Education?What to Know About Online Certificate Programs (Complete Guide)
